어제 신문도 팔까?
Do you think they have
yesterday's Daily News?
왜?
오늘의 운세가 맞나
확인해 보게
I just wanna check my horoscope,
see if it was right.
Oh, my God! Don't Iook now.
Behind you there's a guy...
어머!
돌아보지마
실연의 상처를 준대도
홀딱 빠지고 싶은 남자가 있어
...who can break our hearts
and plunge us into depression.
어디?
꽤 삼삼한데!
Come to mama.
온다!
모른 척 해, 모른 척 해!
He's coming.
Be cool. Be cool. Be cool.
- 모자 예쁘네요
- 고마워요
-Nice hat.
-Thanks.
-We should do something. Whistle.
-I' m not whistling.
그냥 보내면 안돼
한번 불러봐
- 그런 짓 못해
- 불러
Come on, do it!
- 싫어
- 해
Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it.
- 싫어
- 해! 해! 해!
앰뷸런스
시킨다고 하니?
I can't believe you did that.
The One With Mrs. Bing
-It's all my fault.
-No, it's mine.
왜 '우우' 했을까?
대체 뭘 바라고 그랬지?
Why did I whoo-hoo?
Was I hoping
he'd turn around and say...
말 붙이길 기다렸겠지
'아가씨, 내게 관심 있어요?'
... " I Iove that sound.
I must have you now"?
이제 어째야 하는 거지?
I wish there was something
we could do.
이봐요!
이봐, 혼수상태 씨!
Hello, coma guy.
일어나요! 일어나!
Get up, you Girl Scout!
Up, up, up!
무슨 짓이야?
What are you doing?
이렇게라도 해봐야지
Maybe nobody's tried this.
이름이라도 알면 좋겠는데
I wish we at Ieast knew his name.
이름 불명이란 말 싫어
행방불명처럼 들리잖아
I hate that they're
calling him John Doe.
It's so sad. It's Iike he's a deer,
a female deer.
피비
나도 관두려고 했어
Oh, I was gonna stop.
Look at that face.
저 얼굴 좀 봐...
자고 있는 모습도 근사해
Even sleeping he Iooks smart.
손마디를 자세히 봤어?
분명히 화가야
Yeah, but the dents in his knuckles
mean he's artistic.
그럼, 부업으로 조각을 가르치는
변호사라고 생각하자
Okay. He's a Iawyer who teaches
sculpting on the side.
춤도 잘 출걸!
And he can dance.
이 남자 같은 스타일은
여자 말을 잘 들어줄 거야
And he's the kind of guy who,
when you're talking, he's Iistening...
이해한다는 말 대신
섹시한 눈웃음을 던지지!
... not saying, " I understand "...
... but really wondering
what you Iook Iike naked.
관둬!
세상 남자들이 모두
이 남자 같을 순 없을까?
I wish all guys could be Iike him.
이해해
I know.
말이나 돼?
생판 남이잖아
You don't even know this guy.
Are there no conscious men
in the city for you two?
정신없이 누워있는 남자가
그렇게 좋아?
간호해줄 사람이 없어
He doesn't have anyone.
그래, 책임감 때문이야
We feel kind of responsible.
네가 '우우'했다는 게 진짜야?
I can't believe you said "whoo-hoo. "
나도 그런 짓은 안 해
I don't even say "whoo-hoo. "
나온다, 나와!
Oh, she's coming up.
'자유에의 도취'를 쓴, 저자
노라 빙을 만나봅니다
When we return, we 'll talk with
the always interesting Nora Tyler Bing.
애들은 빨리 재우시고
광고 후에 뵙죠
Put the kids to bed for this one.
이거 보지 말자
Don't watch this. Weekend at Bernie 's
is on Showtime and HBO.
'버니스의 주말'이
각 채널마다 다 나와
안돼! 이거 봐
No way.
왜 그래, 너희 엄마신데
-She's your mom.
-Exactly. Weekend at Bernie 's.
그게 문제야
'버니스의 주말'이 나아
한 남자가 앰뷸런스에
2, 30번 치이는 얘기래
Dead guy getting hit
in the groin 20, 30 times.
챈들러, 진심이야
I gotta tell you,
I Iove your mom's books.
난 너의 엄마 책이 좋아
정말이야
여행갈 때도 꼭 들고 간다구
I can't get on a plane without one.
This is so cool.
너무 좋아!
You wouldn't think so
if you were 1 1...
그래도 11살 나이에
내 친구들이 책을 보면서
...and your friends were passing around
page 79 of Mistress Bitch.
야한 아줌마야라고
말하면, 좋진 않을걸
나도 읽은 기억이 나
I remember page 79.
와!
오페라가 끝나고
여자 엉덩이 나오는 거?
The thing after the opera
with the girl with the trick hip?
난 너네 엄마 좋아
대단하신 분이야
I Iove your mom.
I think she's a blast.
친구 엄마라고
추켜세우지마
That's because she's not your mom.
그러지마...
Oh, please. She's the
안녕, 자기
Hi, sweetie.
저 스파게티는 언제 온 거야?
When did " Rigatoni " get back from Rome?
- 어제 밤에
- 그래?
-Last night.
-Really?
저 친구가 탄 비행기가
폭발하지 않았구나?
So, his plane didn't explode
in a big ball of fire?
그런 꿈을 꿨거든
Just a dream I had.
아쉽네!
But, phew!
얘들아, 시작이야
Hey, she's on.
노라 빙!
Nora Bing.
책 얘기를 해보죠
Back to the book. What is this
about you being arrested in London?
런던에서 체포됐다는 게
사실입니까? 왜죠?
Your mom was arrested?
그랬었니?
I'm busy beaming with pride.
자랑스런 얘기 좀 들어보자
좀 쑥스러운 얘긴데요
저는 남자랑 자고 나면...
This is kind of embarrassing...
...but occasionally, after
I've been intimate with a man...
쑥스러운데 저런 말을 해?
Why would she say that's embarrassing?
중국식 닭 요리가 당겨요
...I just get this craving
for kung pao chicken.
그게 방송에서 할 말이에요?
That's too much information.
말할 것도 없이
엄청난 팁을 줬죠
Needless to say, he got a huge tip.
여사님, 사랑해요!
Oh, God, I Iove her!
나 심장발작 직전이야
I think I' m having a stroke.
책 홍보는 어떻습니까?
So how is your book tour going?
좋아요, 곧 뉴욕으로 가요
Oh, fine. I'm leaving
for New York tomorrow, which I hate.
별로 내키지는 않지만
사랑하는 아들을 만나러 가죠
But I get to see my son, who I love.
This is the way that I find out.
Most moms use the phone.
우리 엄마는 저래
보통 엄마들은 전화라도 하지
오해는 말고 들으세요
엄마라는 말이 생소한데요
Don 't take this wrong, I just
don 't see you as a mom.
나쁜 엄마라는 건 아니고...
-I don 't mean that bad.
-Oh, no. I'm a fabulous mom.
아뇨!
저는 좋은 엄마예요
우리 아들 콘돔도
제가 사줬거든요
I bought my son his first condoms.
내 인생이 그렇게 시작됐지
And then he burst into flames.
Let's see. Congress is debating
a new deficit-reduction bill.
의회는 새로운 조세 법안을
검토중이다
시장은 지하철 요금을
올리려 한다
The mayor wants to raise subway fares.
The high today was 45.
오늘 최고 기온은 7도
운동 팀이 운동을 한다
And teams played sports.
피비가 사랑을 담아
글렌 어때?
그 이름이 어울리지?
What about GIen?
He could be a GIen.
너무 평범해
Not special enough.
How about Agamemnon?
'아가멤논'은 어때?
너무 튄다, 얘
Way too special.
I'm famished. What do I want?
배고파 죽겠다
뭘 먹을까?
닭 요리만 빼고
주문하세요
PIease, God, don't Iet it be
kung pao chicken.
You watched the show.
What did you think?
방송 봤구나! 어땠니?
I think you need to come out
of your shell.
조금 만 더 솔직하지
그러셨어요?
What is this dive?
너무 화려한 거 아냐?
분명히 아줌마가 고르셨죠?
Only you could've picked this place.
Come on. Shut up. It's fun.
Give me a hug.
너무 반갑구나
- 잘 지내셨죠?
- 어디 좀 보자
I heard about the divorce.
Lesbian, huh?
- 이혼했다며? 레즈비언이라구?
- 네
너희들은 너무 많은 걸
바라지 말고 살아라
Well, you know what they say:
Be careful what you wish for.
이제 데킬라 주문할까?
-I think we' re ready for some tequila.
-I know I am.
좋으실 대로요
마실 사람?
-Who's doing shots?
-Hit me.
- 저요
- 저두요
좋아, 로스는?
There you go. Ross?
저는 데킬라만 안 마셔요
I' m not really a shot-drinking
kind of guy.
안녕!
늦어서 죄송해요
Hi. Sorry we' re Iate.
둘이 있으면
시간을 잊어버려요
We kind of just, you know,
Iost track of time.
사나이 결심이 바뀌기도 하지
But a man can change.
정확한 감정을 원하십니까?
Anyone want me to appraise anything?
Well, I' m gonna go to tinker-town.
난 작은 것 좀 빼고 올게
여사님 책은 전부 다
읽었어요
Mrs. Bing, I've read
everything you've written.
정말이에요
When I read Euphoria at Midnight,
I wanted to become a writer.
'한밤의 행복'을 읽고
저도 글을 쓰고 싶었어요
잘 들으렴
내가 썼다면, 너도 할 수 있어
Oh, please.
If I can do it, anybody can.
우선 유럽의 도시들을 돌아보고
남자 성을 30가지로 표현해봐
Start with half a dozen
European cities...
...throw in 30 euphemisms
for male genitalia...
...and you've got yourself a book.
그럼 네 책을 갖게 될 거야
챈들러 어머니
말씀이었습니다
My mother, Iadies and gentlemen.
226호로 온 전화는요?
Yeah, any messages for room 226?
- 괜찮니, 로스?
- 네, 괜찮아요
-You okay, slugger?
-Oh, yeah. I' m fine.
오늘 이상하구나
What is with you tonight?
아무 것도 아니에요
Nothing. Nothing, nothing.
네, 고마워요
Okay, thank you.
손에 뽀뽀하던
그 이태리 남자 때문이지?
It's the Italian hand-Iicker, isn't it?
아뇨, 그 손의 주인이요
No. It's the one he's Iicking.
레이첼은 너랑 더 잘 어울려
She's supposed to be with you.
좋은 말씀이네요
You' re good.
내 책이 왜 백만 부씩이나
팔렸는지 아니?
I have sold 1 00 million copies
of my books, and you know why?
The girl on the cover
with her nipples showing?
책표지의 비키니 여자
때문이죠?
아냐, 내 책엔 여자가 사랑에
빠지는 남자가 있기 때문이야
No, because I know how to write men
that women fall in Iove with.
나 같으면,
파올로에 대해 쓰지 않아
I cannot sell a Paolo.
독자들은 파올로 같은 남자의
끝은 궁금해하지 않아
People will not turn 325 pages
for a Paolo.
Come on. The guy's
a secondary character.
그런 남자는 스쳐갈 뿐이야
He's just a complication
you eventually kill off.
주인공인 네가 처리할
조연이라구
언제요?
When?
He's not a hero.
그는 주인공이 아냐
You know who our hero is?
그럼 누가 주인공이게?
The guy on the cover
with his nipples showing?
책표지에 있는 건장한 남자요
No, it's you.
- 아니, 너야
- 위로하지 마세요
-PIease.
-No, really.
아니, 정말이야
넌 똑똑하고, 섹시해
Come on. You' re smart. You' re sexy.
-Right.
-Yes, you are.
알았어요
네가 그걸 모른다는 게
널 섹시해 보이게 만들지
The fact that you don't think you are
makes you sexier.
이만 가자
Come on, kiddo.
You' re gonna be fine, believe me.
넌 분명히 잘될 거야
그냥 밖에서 쌀게요
I'II just pee in the street.
- 챈들러 있어?
- 응
Is Chandler here?
Wait. Come here.
어제 밤 일...
Okay, about Iast night...
...you know...
챈들러한테 말 안 했지?
말할 필요도 없는 일이잖아
... Chandler, you didn't tell....
We don't need to tell Chandler.
It was just a kiss. No big deal, right?
그냥 뽀뽀였어, 뽀뽀 알지?
별거 아니잖아
- 응, 별거 아냐
- 됐어
Right. No big deal.
희한한 세상이야!
In bizarro world.
넌 금기를 깼어
You broke the code.
뭔 금기?
-What code?
-You don't kiss your friend's mom.
친구 엄마랑 키스는 안 돼
친구 누나는 괜찮아...
Sisters are okay.
Maybe a hot-Iooking aunt.
이모까지도 봐주겠지만
엄마는 안돼!
But not a mom. Never a mom.
절대 안돼!
복도에 서서 뭐해?
What are you guys doing out here?
조이한테 아침에 라켓볼 치러
다니자고 했었거든
Joey and I had discussed getting
in an early morning racquetball game.
맞아
그런데 늦잠을 잤어
But apparently somebody overslept.
그런데 넌 라켓이 없잖아
Well, you don't have your racquet.
줄만 새로 갈면 돼
No. No, I don't
because it's being restrung.
얘가 새로 줄을 갈아준댔어
Somebody was supposed to bring me one.
그래?
일단, 네 라켓 구경 좀 하자
Well, you didn't call
and Ieave your grip size.
오래된 친구도
문제가 생기는 구나
You guys are spending
way too much time together.
그래, 난 인간 쓰레기야!
I' m scum. I' m scum.
- 어떻게 그럴 수 있냐?
- 몰라
-How could you Iet this happen?
-I don't know.
솔직히 보통 엄마는 아니잖아
그분은, 그분은 섹시해
It's not Iike she's a regular mom.
She's sexy. She's....
우리 엄마는 안 섹시해?
You don't think my mom's sexy?
약간 다른 차원이지
Well, not in the same way.
우리 엄마, 글로리아 여사님도
한창 땐 아름다웠어
I'II have you know, GIoria T ribbiani
was a handsome woman in her day.
너도 애를 일곱씩이나 낳아봐
You think it's easy giving birth
to seven children?
- 우리 대화가 좀 이상하게 샜다
- 맞아
Okay, I think we're getting
into a weird area here.
- 안녕
여기서 뭐해?
What are you doing here?
그게...
라켓볼 치지 말자구
Not playing racquetball.
얘 라켓은 구경도 못했다
-He forgot to Ieave his grip size.
-He didn't get the goggles.
- 얘는 고글도 안 샀대
- 고맙다, 친구야
둘이 무슨 문제가 있구나
Sounds Iike you two have issues.
- 잘 가, 자기야
- 잘 있어
Goodbye, baby.
저걸 똑바로 쳐다봐야 돼나?
Do they wait for me to do this?
그럼 말 할 거지?
-Are you gonna tell him?
-Why would I tell him?
아니, 말 안 할 거야
꼭 해야되는 거야?
걔네 엄마가
먼저 말하면 어쩔래?
If you don't, his mother might.
아침부터 뭔 일이야?
What are you guys doing here?
얘가 운동복도 안 입었어
He's not even wearing a jock strap.
내 질문이 뭐였지?
What did I ask?
- 안녕!
여기서 뭐해?
What are you doing here?
그냥 잠깐 들러서...
Nothing. I just thought
I'd stop by, you know, after...
...that I, you know.
그런데 넌 웬일이야?
So, what are you doing here?
오고 싶어서 온 게 아냐
I' m not really here.
이거나 놓고 가려고 들렀어...
I just thought I'd drop these off
on the way. My way.
Do you come here a Iot...
너 혼자 자주 오니?
...without me?
아니, 아냐
No, no, no.
Do you think he's doing any better
than he was this morning?
오늘 아침보다
차도가 있어 보이니?
내가 어떻게 알아?
How would I know? I wasn't here.
- 난 온 적 없는데
- 그래?
Really? Not even
to change his pajamas?
그럼 혼자 갈아입었니?
세상에!
Oh, my God.
친구로서 솔직하고 싶었어
You're my friend.
I had to tell you.
믿을 수가 없어
I can't believe it.
파올로가 키스를?
Paolo kissed my mom?
그날 봤는지 모르겠지만
파올로는 많이 취했었어
I don't know if you noticed,
but he drank a Iot.
I mean, you know how he gets
그 녀석 취하면 좀...
더는 못하겠다
I can't do this. I did it.
나야, 나라구, 미안해
내가 네 엄마한테 키스했어
It was me. I' m sorry.
I kissed your mom.
뭐?
What?
레이첼과 파올로 때문에
화가 나서 술을 많이 마셨어
I was upset about Rachel and
I had too much tequila, and Nora...
노라가, 여사님이...
너의 엄마가...
... Mrs. Mom, your Bing, was...
위로해주셨어
... being nice.
But nothing happened.
큰일은 없었어
조이한테 물어봐
Nothing. Ask Joey.
- 화장실 가느라고...
- 알고 있었어?
-Joey came in
-You knew about this?
아는 게 병이란
속담이 있지
You know, knowledge is a tricky thing.
한 집에 사는 나한테
얘기 안 한 이유가 뭐야?
Why didn't you tell me?
다행이라고 생각해
현장이 잡히니까 털어놓잖아?
You're Iucky I caught them, or else
who knows what would've happened?
고맙다, 난 죽었어
Thanks, man. Big help.
What the hell were you thinking?
대체 뭔 짓이야!
생각이 있는 거야?
생각이 없었지, 난...
I wasn't. I don't know. I
너희가 친한 친구라 해도
우리 엄마와 나의 관계는 몰라
No one knows the crap I go through
with my mom more than you.
그래
-I know.
-I can't believe you did this.
- 정말 환장하겠네
- 챈들러
- 이해해
- 말 안한 너도 똑같아
-Me neither.
-I' m mad at you too.
- 왜 나한테 화를 내냐?
- 이 문 부숴 버려?
-Why are you mad at me?
-Let me slam the door.
내가 아니라
저 녀석 짓이야!
I didn't kiss her. See what happens
when you break the code?
내가 금기라고 했지?
조이!
레이첼
왔니?
'파멸의 여인'
레이첼 그린 지음
"A Woman Undone,
by Rachel IKaren Greene. "
일단 시작해봤어
1장을 쓰는 중이야
I thought I'd give it a shot.
I'm on the first chapter.
'그의 바지 지퍼 속에서
사랑이 펼쳐진다'
Do you think his "Iove stick" can be
"Iiberated from its denim prison"?
응, 좋은 거 같아
Yeah, I'd say so.
그런데 '짚어'가 아니라
'지퍼'야
And there's no "J " in "engorged. "
레이첼!
- 너 왔니?
- 안녕
오늘밤에 병원 갈거니?
-You going to the hospital tonight?
-No. You?
아니, 넌?
No. You?
네가 물었잖아
You just asked me.
심도 있는 질문이었어
Maybe it was a trick question.
- 레이첼, 지금 시작할까?
- 그래
Rachel, can we do this now?
너무 신난다
I am so hot.
부모님 결혼식 사진이야
Here's my mom and dad
on their wedding day.
Now, you tell me she's not a knockout.
우리 엄마도 죽여줬지?
언제까지 이런 대화를
해야되니?
-I can't believe this conversation.
-Just try to picture her not pregnant.
그냥 우리 엄마가 임신중이
아니라고 생각해봐
센트럴 퍼크가 자랑하는
피비 부페이입니다
Central Perk is proud to present
Miss Phoebe Buffay.
감사합니다
Thanks.
오늘 노래는 최근에 만난
어떤 남자에 관한 겁니다
I'd Iike to start with a song
about a man I recently met...
제겐 소중한 남자죠
...who's come to be
very important to me.
내 연인이 되기 위해
눈을 뜰 필요는 없어요
You don 't have to be awake
To be my man
뇌파가 움직이는 한
언제나 손을 잡아 줄게요
Long as you have brain waves
I'll be there to hold your hand
만난 지 얼마 되지 않았지만
이 말을 해주고 싶어요
Though we just met the other day
There 's something I have got to say
대단히 감사합니다
잠깐 쉬었다 하죠
Thank you very much.
I' m gonna take a short break.
피비의 노래였습니다
That was Phoebe Buffay, everybody.
-What the hell was that?
-Phoebe just started
왜들 저래?
- 피비가 지금...
- 난 조이한테 물었어
I was talking to Joey.
AII right, there, mother-kisser?
금기의 왕자!
금기의 왕자
" Mother-kisser. "
닥칠게
I'II shut up.
챈들러, 할 말이 있어
아직도 화나 있는 거 알아
I know you' re still mad at me...
... but there were two people
there that night.
그날 밤, 한 장소에
두 사람이 있었어
그리고 두 입술이 있었지
-There were two sets of Iips.
-I expect this from her.
그래, 난 우리 엄마한테
무의식의 성이란 말을 듣고 컸어
She's always been a Freudian nightmare.
엄마가 늘 그런 식이라면
말씀을 드려야지
Then why don't you say something?
그렇게 간단치 않아
복잡하다구!
Because it's complicated.
It's complex.
넌 엄마랑 키스한 놈이야
You kissed my mom.
그리스 신화극 연습이에요
We' re rehearsing a Greek play.
That's funny.
Are we done now?
- 순발력 좋네, 말 다 했어?
- 아니!
어머니께 당신 아들 감정이
어떤지 말씀을 드려야지
You mean you' re not gonna
tell her how you feel?
말 안 할 거야
Just because you played
tonsil tennis with my mom...
우리 엄마랑 키스 좀 했다고
다 안다는 생각이 드냐?
...doesn't mean you know her.
You can't talk to her.
너도 말 못 할거다
Okay. "You can't"?
Or you can't?
나야, 너야?
그건 내 손가락이야
Okay, that's my finger.
그래, 이건 내 무릎이다
Okay, that's my knee.
아직 연습 중이에요
Still doing the play.
어디다 숨겼니?
What did you do with him?
깨어났군요!
-You're awake.
-Look at you.
지금 기분이 어때요?
How do you feel?
약간 멍하지만 괜찮아요
A Iittle woozy, but basically okay.
- 정말 잘 됐어요
- 저도 좋아요
Gosh, you Iook good.
I feel good.
- 누구시죠?
- 미안해요
Who are you?
-Sorry.
-I'm Phoebe.
- 저는 피비 부페이예요
- 저는 모니카 겔러
I' m Monica.
I've been caring for you.
- 당신을 간호했어요
- 우리 둘 다요
We both have.
- 저 그림 당신들 솜씨예요?
- 제가 한 거예요
-The Etch A Sketch is from you?
-Actually, me.
발 마사지는 제가 했구요
-I got you the foot massager.
-I shaved you.
면도는 누가 했게요?
나예요
- 난 신문을 읽어줬죠
- 난 노래를 했죠
-I read to you.
-I sang.
고마워요
Well, thanks.
- 고맙긴요
- 별거 아니죠
-Oh, my pleasure.
-You' re welcome.
그럼 다음에 뵙죠
So I guess I'II see you around.
그뿐이에요?
What? That's it?
- 다음에 봐요?
- 그럼 무슨 말을 하죠?
"See you around "?
-What do you want me to say?
-I don't know.
글쎄요...
참 친절하군요
Maybe...
... "That was nice. "
내게 잘해줬군요
" It meant something to me. "
전화 드릴게요
" I'II call you. "
네, 전화할게요
-Okay. I'II call you.
-I don't think you mean that.
진심이 아니죠?
전형적인 남자로군
This is so typical.
우린 베풀고, 베풀고
또 베풀었는데
You know, we give and we give...
...and we give.
우리가 받을 건 없어
And we just get nothing back.
깨어나서 기껏 한다는 말이
"다음에 봐요!"라니
And then one day, you wake up,
and it's, "See you around. "
가자, 피비
Let's go, Phoebe.
이거 알아요?
You know what?
We thought you were different.
당신은 다르다고 생각했는데
그냥 혼수상태일 뿐이었어요
But I guess it was just the coma.
안녕, 꼬맹아
The car's waiting. I just wanted
to drop off my book for your friends.
네 친구들에게 책을
주려고 잠깐 들렀어
서명은 했으니까
작별의 뽀뽀만 하면 돼
Autographed.
And give you a goodbye kiss.
이제 뽀뽀하고
인사만 하면 된다
Here's the kiss,
here's the goodbye....
리스본 가서 선물 보낼까?
-Anything you want from Lisbon?
-Just knowing you' re there is enough.
아뇨
도착하면 전화나 주세요
그래, 그럼 잘 있어라
사랑한다
AII right. Well, be good.
I Iove you.
로스와 키스하셨죠?
You kissed my best Ross.
아님 뽀뽀인가요?
Or something to that effect.
그건 실수였다
Look, it was stupid.
- 큰 실수죠
- 큰 실수였어
-Really stupid.
이유는 모르겠어
I don't even know how it happened.
미안하다
앞으로 그런 일 없을 거야
I' m sorry, honey. I promise
it will never happen again.
- 무지하게 큰 실수죠
- 맞아, 큰 실수야
Really, really stupid.
이제 됐지?
-Are we okay now?
-Yeah.
네
아뇨, 아뇨
No.
금지된 사랑과
그 집 문짝!
The forbidden Iove
of a man and his door.
말했어
He told her off. And not just
about the kiss.
키스 얘기 뿐 아니라 전부다
- 농담이지?
- 아냐, 들어봐
You're kidding?
He said, "When are you gonna
start being a mom? "
"언제 철들어서
엄마가 될 거죠?"
그랬더니 엄마가...
Then she said:
"The question is, when are you gonna
realize I have a bomb? "
"넌 언제 철들어서
엄마를 인수할래?"
혹시 이런 말 아냐?
Are you sure she didn't say:
"넌 언제 철들어서
엄마로 인정할래?"
"When are you gonna grow up
and realize I am your mom? "
그게 말 된다
-That makes more sense.
-You think?
그렇지?
What's going on now?
지금 상황은 어때?
몰라, 지금 너한테
문장 강의 듣고 있잖아
I don't know. I've been standing here
spelling it out for you.
아무 소리 안 들려
I don't hear anything. Wait.
잠깐, 잠깐만...
뭐가 보여?
What do you see?
너무 작고, 거꾸로 보여서
잘 모르겠어
It's hard to tell.
They're tiny and upside down.
가만, 가만!
Wait, wait, wait.
둘이 걷는다
저쪽으로...
They're walking away.
아냐, 우리 쪽이야
도망가!
No, they' re not. They' re coming
right at us. Run!
- 괜찮지, 얘야?
- 네, 괜찮아요
-Are you okay, kiddo?
-Yeah, I' m okay.
그래, 잘 있어
AII right. You be good.
운전 조심하세요
Drive safe.
-Mrs. Bing.
-Mr. Geller.
- 빙 부인?
- 겔러 군?
친구!
나한테 한 말이야?
You mean that?
그럼, 당연하지
Yeah, why not?
So I told her.
말씀드렸어
어땠어?
-How did it go?
-Awful. Awful.
끔찍했어
최악의 대화였지
Couldn't have gone worse.
- 넌 기분이 어때?
- 아주 좋아
-Well, how do you feel?
-Pretty good.
대화를 했어
I told her.
내 생각이 괜찮았지?
너희 엄마랑 키스한 거 말이야
Well, see?
So maybe it wasn't such a bad idea,
me kissing your mom, huh?
물론, 대화를 시작하는
방법은 많이 있지
But we don't have to
go down that road.
받아
드디어 1장을 마쳤어
읽어보고, 솔직히 말해 줘
This is just the first chapter...
...and I want your absolute
honest opinion. Okay?
참, 2페이지의 '부푼 기슴'은
'부픈 가슴'이야
And on page two, he's not reaching
for her " heaving beasts. "
She could have heaving beasts.
왜 가슴이 부풀었어?
그걸 말로 해야 아니?
Right, but in this case she doesn't.
'젓곡찌'가 뭐야?
What's a " niffle"?
'부픈 기슴'마다 다
달려있는 거
You can usually find them
on the heaving beasts.
알았어
난 자판에 익숙지 않아
Okay, so I' m not a great typist.
그녀에게 바치는 꼬치
곧 그의 욕망이다
Did you get to the part
about his "huge, throbbing pens"?
You don't wanna be around
when he starts writing with those.
어떤 꼬치인지는 몰라도
난 절대 안 먹을 거야
됐어, 도로 내놔!
That's it. Give them back.
잠깐, 기다려봐
숨어있는 털도 있대
Wait, I just got to the part
about her "public hair. "